Aa ...
You
are all the same as he, as I am.
All the same people.
What won't you show?
Do you understand?
Here in
Donetsk
we
have
someone,
...
someone, someone,
someone,
What are you doing?
What are
you doing?
Look, Yaroslavich!
This is the Central Committee of the fucking faggot, look.
Not.
Maybe we should go to the director
now, like, that
we are fixing the right... There, in.
The beads are pushing him, bitch.
Look at
this Yaroslavich's beads, damn it. Is
he fucking crazy or something?
Fucking
hell.
Yes, he is being pushed into the minibuses.
This is
Kremenchuk, Kyiv.
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go!
Let him go!
Fuck the
balloon!
Drive the car, please!
Drive the car!
Remove the balloon!
Step away from the car, please.
This policeman is normal.
Get away from the car! Soul! Soul!
Soul!
Get away from the car!
Let him go! Let him go!
Let go Let him go!
Let him go!
Please come
here!
Bear, what are you doing?
Come here and help me, please!
Just wait, please!
People, please help!
Bear, what are you doing?
Get behind
the wheel!
Get behind the wheel! Get behind the wheel!
Get behind the wheel!
What are you doing, huh?
People, call the police!
Let's all do it!
Look at all!
Call the police!
You fucking faggot beat me!
Guys, you are out of uniform,
what are you doing?
You will break the boy!
Fuck, there's a little fucker there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no,
no,
no.
Guys!
What are you doing? Calm down!
I want
to live! What am I doing?
I want to live!
Are you killing him? I can't, guys,
I can't! Get rid of him!
Are you hungry?
Are you killing him? I can't,
guys, I can't!
Ruki! Guys, I can't!
What are you doing? Hands!
What are you doing?
Hands!
Hooray!
Prove it,
come on, prove it!
Calm down! Calm down!
Calm down!
What are you doing?
Why are you hitting me in the face?
Give the man some peace!
What are you doing?
Where do you kick?
This is an article!
What are you doing?
Get up on your feet!
Guys, you're
going to fucking Odessa now! You're
going to have problems, do you
hear me? Where are you going?
Now I'm going to fuck you, bitch, with
the floor! Do you understand, my people? How,
how did you fuck him? Fucking hell, take
it!
Get up on your feet!
Well, go to the department, damn it!
They seem to be
the police, but I don't
understand what the fuck you're
doing, and business! What's wrong with you? Are
you fucking nuts? I'm shocked!
Oh my!
What are you doing? You're a fucking idiot!
Why are you talking like that?
What is he doing?
He kicks him in the head, damn it!
What are you, a common man, huh?
Get on the bridge!
Yes, police, this is an experiment!
There are few of you!
Call in a couple more patrols!
What the fuck are you talking about?
Can't cope with an
elderly person?
His heart
will stop now, do you
know where it will be?
Why are you kicking him?
Will you explain to
me why you are kicking him?
On the head, on the face.
He's old enough to be your
father, young man. Aren't you
ashamed?
Kicks him in the face.
And you ask why?
I'm not going with this,
I'll go to the police.
What should they do?
Did he attack you?
He attacked you? Wait!
He took him in the face, with his
feet in the face!
Look at this
grown man!
What are you doing?
People, help this man!
Well, please
put it down!
Go ahead and hit him again!
Come on, hit him again!
I'm not going anywhere!
Wait!
What are you doing?
What kind of chaos is this?
Why beat him?
How does it not hit?
He kicked him, I saw
how he, the bitch,
kicked him, fucking.
For what? Let the man explain.
Go, go, go.
I didn’t realize it myself.
I don't have a child, who
is still a minor.
Where are they infecting you?
What did he do?
Nobody is mobilizing, he is 50,
wanted, report, write,
wanted.
Why hit? Why?
Call!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Help!
People want to order!
People, help!
Why are you dragging it out?
Who attacked people?
We are all with the bandits...
bandits...
We are all with the bandits... We are all with.
Bandits...
We are all with the bandits... We are all.
With bandits... bandits...
We are all with the bandits...
We are all with the bandits... We are.
All with the bandits...
We are all with the bandits...
We are all with the bandits... We are all.
Why would you kill everyone?
I
don't resist!
I don't resist!
I don't resist,
people!
Come on, let me get up! Give me your hand! Give me your hand!
I'm not resisting! Give up your hand, I
said!
Put your hand behind the wall!
Put your hand behind the wall! Help, people!
People, help!
People! Put your hand here!
Wait! Hand!
I give you my hand!
Help!
That's it, oh my God!
I have
the right, you, you wait, you
don’t find the cameras?
You can't find the cameras?
You don't find any cameras?
You can't find the cameras? All of you,
his poor memory.
Let's do it this way, maybe it's not bad.
Help!
Inexpensive! Help!
Stop!
Stop! What are you doing?
Take her already!
That's it,
hot water is coming out of the tap.
The packaging
has begun.
Oh!
It's hitting!
That's it, we're all fucking gone.
They beat the boy.
Let him go! Let him go!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
They beat,
beat and beat, men beat,
just beat.
I still have a working car near the garage.
What should I do?
Maybe we should go?
No, stop.
Help! Help!
Help!
Help! Help! Help!
Help! Help!
Shiyanov Alexander Sergeevich, V.
What are you accused of?
For committing a terrorist act
of illegally crossing the border
of the Russian Federation with weapons
for the purpose of intimidating the
civilian population of
the Kursk region.
Do you admit your guilt?
I admit my guilt.
Fire!
Fire! Fire!
Hold on!
This is the capture
team!
This is the capture team!
Something is happening!
No-no-no,
guys! No-no-no! People!
Come on, bitch.